svtuition.org 2019-06-12

# Privacy Policy | Accounting Education

**1\. What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form or comment on the site. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or website URL. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**2\. What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. To personalize your experience
  2. To improve our website 
  3. To improve customer service 
  4. To send periodic emails

**3\. How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**4\. Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party  advertised products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**6\. Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

7\. Transparency

If you are not interested in third party ads, you can block ads with ads blocker apps or google chrome extension. After ad blocker, you will still see our ebook and course ads. When you buy or enroll our course, we get earning and we can do better for our free online education mission or you can donate at [here](http://www.svtuition.com/p/donate-how-can-i-donate-1.html).

  * A conspicuous hyper-link to an NAI-approved Opt-Out mechanism for Interest-Based Advertising
  * Data may be collected for the purpose of Interest-Based Advertising on the property.
  *  We disclose to readers and visitors of our site that we endorse a product or service and have a “material connection” to the seller. We’re using affiliated links for monetizing our page of website.
  * We also monetizing our apps  with ads.
